If There Be Thorns is a tv movie, thriller, drama film directed by Nancy Savoca.
Christopher and Cathy Dollanganger live together as man and wife with Cathy's two sons
who are unaware of the incestuous nature of their parents' relationship.
But when a mysterious woman moves in next door and befriends the younger boy, Bart, he begins a
strange transformation and displays accusatory behavior towards Cathy and Christopher.
When Christopher discovers their mysterious neighbor is, in fact, his mother Corrine
Dollanganger, all of the family's long-hidden secrets are revealed in a tragic climax.
Corrine, played by Heather Graham.
Cathy, played by Rachael Carpani.
Christopher, played by Jason Lewis.
Bart, played by Mason Cook.
Jory, played by Jedidiah Goodacre.
Melodie, played by Emily Tennant.
If There Be Thorns is a 2015 television film based on the
best-selling 1981 novel of the same name.
It premiered on April 5, 2015, and was produced by Lifetime.
Seeds of Yesterday is the sequel film based on the novel of the same name.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, incest, woman director.
The tone is emotional and intense.